StellarFund — cross-border crowdfunding on Stellar.
Someone in Germany can fund a bakery in Kenya in seconds, for cents.
Funds sit in a smart contract and release as milestones are met.
Discovery: search and category filters; campaigns have titles, images and categories.
Active and past campaigns are separated for clarity.
Onboarding is one tap: Connect a wallet…
…then "Get Test USDC" — it funds the account, sets the USDC trustline and mints 500 test USDC.
Create a campaign with a title, description, category, cover image and milestones.
The campaign is deployed on-chain; its identity is saved off-chain.
Open a campaign and see the milestone timeline.
Contribute in USDC — a real, wallet-signed transaction. Contributions are capped at the goal.
The Proof board lists every unique backer wallet, with links to stellar.expert.
Every interaction is permanent and publicly verifiable on Stellar Testnet.
When a milestone is approved, the creator releases that tranche of funds.
The fiat ramp runs the real SEP-10 and SEP-24 protocol against a Stellar test anchor.
Pay fiat, receive USDC — and back to fiat on withdrawal. No real money; testnet only.
A private analytics dashboard shows live, on-chain stats by category and top campaigns.
Architecture: a Factory deploys each Escrow, which records success in a Reputation contract.
Six wallets plus WalletConnect, English and Turkish, analytics, and a PWA.
Next: creator profiles, comments and updates, notifications, and a path to mainnet.
StellarFund — fund anyone, anywhere.